{
    "subject": "resource/Tom_Jones_(singer)",
    "predicate": "property/birthDate",
    "object": "1940-06-07",
    "human_readable": "Tom Jones was born on June 7, 1940.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8557828068733215,
            "question": "June 7th corresponds to what year for Tom Jones' birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8269339203834534,
            "question": "When was Tom Jones born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6699584722518921,
            "question": "What is Tom Jones's birthdate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6388850808143616,
            "question": "On which day of the month was Tom Jones born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4914877116680145,
            "question": "Tom Jones' birth date falls in which season?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4417788088321686,
            "question": "In what year did Tom Jones come into the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4013269543647766,
            "question": "What is Tom Jones's birth month?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32923880219459534,
            "question": "Calculate Tom Jones's age."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28130611777305603,
            "question": "Is Tom Jones older than or younger than 83 years old?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.2704666256904602,
            "question": "If today is July 15th, 2023, how old would Tom Jones be?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tom Jones was born on June 7, 1940.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4540_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Tom Jones older than or younger than 83 years old?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4540_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Calculate Tom Jones's age.",
            "html": "dbpedia_4540_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is Tom Jones's birth month?",
            "html": "dbpedia_4540_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_59.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_4540_86.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe reason for this response is that all four documents mention Tom Jones' birthdate as June 7, 1940. There are no conflicting information or evidence to suggest that he was born on a different date."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis answer is derived from the information provided across multiple documents where it is consistently mentioned that Sir Tom Jones, whose birth name is Thomas John Woodward, was born on June 7, 1940."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}